today is Christmas Eve and Sonic was the
happiest Hedgehog in the world two moro
Claus Christmas he would certainly not
be bored it was his most favorite
holiday season why is it his favorite
you ask perhaps being able to buy his
lover a present was the reason but there
was a problem he forgot to buy a gift
for his lover he doesn't want his lover
to discover just then Bartleby came down
the stairs I in Sonic splat what are you
doing the sexy man said Oh Bart will be
Sonic said has he turned to his
boyfriend I was just admiring the
Christmas tree it is very beautiful
don't you want to come see haha yes it
is very pretty although I think you
operate a obeyed wouldn't you agree the
compliment made Sonic blush his cheeks
turned as red as a cherry I'll be right
back Bart levy said Sonic as he ran out
the front door he ran as fast as he
could perhaps wall mode is still open he
thought to himself he could buy
chocolates or maybe a new bookshelf he
was happy to be on a way to buy a
present for his lover he wanted to buy a
present like no other suddenly almost
out of nowhere he heard the sound of a
car screeching toward him oh no Sonic
said get out of my way get out of my way
right now but it was too late the driver
could not see him
[Music]
the car was broken into hundreds of
pieces and Sonic lay motionless on the
ground but thankfully Knuckles and Manic
we're passing by Sonic the Hedgehog was
found by some Christmas miracle the car
had missed Sonic entirely it's get off
the road and hit a tree hey bro Sonic
said do you want to go to walmart with
me I'm going to buy a present for
Bartleby Knuckles and Manic of course
agreed who wouldn't want to help Sonic
with his Christmas shopping the three
friends may their way to walmart if they
are lucky it might just still be open
and it was the search for the perfect
Christmas present was on Sonic look down
every aisle but just couldn't find the
perfect gift is there any hope left just
when he was going to give up hope he saw
it the perfect box of chocolates of
course the Hedgehog thought to himself
I'll get him bad it's perfect but it
costs 1999 that is way more money that's
on a cat at the moment just as Sonic was
going to put back Knuckles stepped in
and gave Sonic a twenty-dollar bill I
was going to use this divided presence
for my family but I think you need it
more he said thanks Knuckles Sonic said
as he bought a box of chocolates Sonic
said goodbye to his friends and made his
way back home the fat blue Hedgehog
snuck his way through the house to put
the present under the tree he didn't
want to alert his boyfriend Bartleby but
Bart will be heard him and came down the
stairs to see what made the noise he was
so excited to see a present address to
him Sonic loves seeing his lover so
happy Bart levy immediately went for the
present and attempted to rip it open
right away hehe Oh Bart la vie wait for
Christmas tomorrow you silly Sonic set
with a laughter Bart lebih reluctantly
put it back down and slapped Sonic's but
well then my Beach let's go to Sleet
then we have a big day tomorrow Sonic
blushed and grab Bart Louise head and
they made their way upstairs
us and so excited to see what Santa
brought me tomorrow Sonic said they then
turned out the lights and went off to
bed